{
    "subject": "resource/Percy_the_Small_Engine",
    "predicate": "ontology/voice",
    "object": "resource/Chie_K\u014djiro",
    "human_readable": "Percy the Small Engine is voiced by Chie K\u014djiro.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9383465647697449,
            "question": "Who voices Percy the Small Engine?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8108130693435669,
            "question": "Is Percy the Small Engine a popular character?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7756052017211914,
            "question": "Is Chie K\u014djiro a voice actor?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.734494149684906,
            "question": "What other characters has Chie K\u014djiro voiced?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5865718722343445,
            "question": "What is Chie K\u014djiro known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5797872543334961,
            "question": "What makes Chie K\u014djiro a successful voice actor?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5722012519836426,
            "question": "Where can you hear Chie K\u014djiro's voice acting?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5564619898796082,
            "question": "Can you name any other anime featuring Chie K\u014djiro's voice acting?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.505765974521637,
            "question": "What type of media features Percy the Small Engine?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.16289663314819336,
            "question": "Do you know any other anime characters voiced by Japanese actors?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Percy the Small Engine is voiced by Chie K\u014djiro.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4412_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of media features Percy the Small Engine?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4412_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you name any other anime featuring Chie K\u014djiro's voice acting?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4412_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where can you hear Chie K\u014djiro's voice acting?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4412_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4412_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4412_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4412_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4412_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4412_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4412_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4412_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4412_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4412_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4412_59.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here's the evaluation of the query:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n\nThe reason for this answer is that none of the documents mention Chie K\u014djiro as the voice actor for Percy the Small Engine. In fact, one of the documents mentions Keith Wickham and Martin Sherman as previous voice actors, but not Chie K\u014djiro."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n```\n\nThe documents do not mention any voice actor named Chie K\u014djiro for Percy the Small Engine. The information provided lists different voice actors, including Keith Wickham, Nigel Pilkington, and Christopher Ragland, but there is no reference to Chie K\u014djiro."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "There is no information provided in the context that suggests Percy is voiced by Chie K\u014djiro.",
            "category": 4
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "The provided context lists the voice actors for Percy the Small Engine in both British and US versions, and Chie K\u014djiro is not among them.",
            "category": 4
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "There is no mention of Chie K\u014djiro as a voice actor for Percy the Small Engine in any of the provided context information.",
            "category": 4
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "The context information clearly states that the voice actors for Percy the Small Engine include Keith Wickham (2009-2015), Nigel Pilkington (2015-2021), and Christopher Ragland (2016; singing voice). Chie K\u014djiro is not mentioned as a voice actor for Percy.",
            "category": 4
        }
    }
}